you
Wear flower shoes
Running barefoot
Because it will be me
What...
Now
I can't pretend not to know
Uh...
degradation
Degradation!
Uh, low, uh, low
degradation
What should I do?
Oh, come to your senses, uh...
degradation
- degradation
- Uh, low.
Uh, come on
Please take a closer look, okay?
Is your Mac normal?
Don't worry
Ah...
one here
Why? Why?
It looks like it has some kind of drug on it.
Huh? approximately?
Well, if it’s medicine, no way
Do, do, do, do?
I'm just exhausted and falling asleep
Ah, yes
Okay, I understand, so let’s go.
Huh? That...
Hey, are you awake?
Ah
How am I here?
Ugh?
No, I told you to ask me when I wake up.
What if my memory is dark?
Oh, please explain the whole story.
No, I was having a good time when the cold wind hit me.
Why are you running around in the middle of the night?
Pick pick, fall down, I hope you fall down
Oh no
That...
Let go of this!
No, leave this aside.
The left injury is a must
It will hurt the moon.
While my body changed
I will protect it somehow
If my body comes back
Damn it
Wow
no
If you don't want to talk, you can stop talking.
Why are you swearing all of a sudden?
Oh, where are you?
I'm not even feeling better yet
There is only one way
protecting and neglecting
standing in between
I have no choice but to become cowardly
I guess my body changed like this
Let me get hurt instead of you
All this humiliation
By experiencing it myself
Out of guilt for poverty
Don't go away
Ha, you feel like shit
I'll never know
So
When my body comes back
Don't delay and get out of here
Don’t ever set foot in Hanyang again.
no
No, I just feel like crap
How do I feel? Do I feel like a rich person?
chi
That sarcasm only hurts
What is my sarcasm?
Do you think it will be very fresh?
Oh, really, Mr.
It looks like shit
You are so cowardly.
All this risk
Even though I know it’s because of me
It's like you're hurting me
Let's get some sleep, get some sleep
What the fuck is going on every night?
How cruel! dare now
Hmm, I should avoid neck acupuncture.
Best to avoid it, yeah
Why is it the moon again?
yes
It's best to avoid it
It's best to hide
The left superior
It's a shame that the city has been emptied.
If you know that you failed today
i am dead
About Bakga Dal-i
Bring something
Ah
Wow
degradation
The Great Queen Mother is looking for you.
Ah, just tell me you’re busy.
Well, I have to go anyway.
You're only going to talk about concubines, right?
You're just going to bang on the desk, okay?
No, the high-ranking nobles
I don't know why you hit the desk like that, huh?
What's wrong with the desk, the desk, huh?
Desk, desk...
It's a fertility drug.
ha
How dare this sitting cross the line?
To the manufacturing lady
In the words of the court lady who planted
Bakga Dal-i is finished
I will not take infertility medication
I fought against ten court ladies.
‘Fight back’?
oh
The more I see it, the more I like it.
yes
To become my person
You have to have that level of spirit.
It looks like the manufacturing company is moving again.
What are you going to do?
If the Crown Prince is not a fool
Just a concubine concubine
You probably don't know it's a shield.
very just
If anything catches you
It's right to be a concubine
Like this, you and I
I guess my body has changed
Let me get hurt instead of you
Having experienced all that humiliation myself,
Never out of guilt for poverty
Don't go away
Hmm
There are too many people watching
I don’t think the rice will cook well.
Only one person left, Jimil Nine
Everyone go away
no
Where is Dal going and why...
Ah, bakga boiling water
In preparation for my royal wedding,
I was selected as a member of the royal family.
I don't eat
Take a bite
Counting?
♪ Hide tight
Show your hair ♪
♪ Hide tight, I’ll show your butt ♪
♪ Where have you been hiding?
Did you hide behind the tree ♪
♪ Hang in there ♪
♪ You can hear the sound of urine ♪
♪ Hide tight, let your hair show ♪
degradation
Crown Prince
Oh, huh?
Your Majesty the Lord?
Oh, then we should run now, uh.
Let's count, let's count!
Oh my, my, my, my, my
Please pay tribute to the crown prince.
who what
Did they try to eat me?
Why avoid it, why?
That...
Ah, why isn’t Prince Jeun getting better, huh?
- ah...
- Eat good food
A gentleman who lives in a place
Uh, why isn't it getting better?
Mr. I
Ah, the New Year’s meeting
Are you not going to do it, Mr. Ai?
Oh, if you're that worried.
Please send your condolences.
- Is that okay?
- Yes
why suddenly
Did you send a message?
Could it be that you realized that I was faking it?
I don't think that's the case
The Gyesannyeon incident
What you want to solve quickly is
Seems like a sure thing, right?
Ha, in this situation
If you know the existence of the Cheongguk boy
It's straight, right?
Is there more to do than just run away?
The boy from the Qing Dynasty will take revenge immediately.
It's going wild
Don't follow today
I need you to keep an eye on me.
yes
Please, if you just hold out until the national wedding,
Woohee becoming a slave
I can stop it
Even if it's nothing short of cowardly
there is no way
Wow
Then I'll leave
I can't avoid it this time
Jeundaegun Nari is all healed.
Yeah, when the body
I might come back
I can’t just postpone revenge.
Yeah, I got it.
let's go
In the settings I set
There is no such thing as poor beauty
Ah
Tie me up
Hey Naekwan Yoon
Please tie the hat strap for me.
- Sedol
- Yes?
If gold floats in water
Do you know what it is called?
Suddenly that
What are you talking about?
- Correct answer
- What is it?
Because there was crack in the water
Ah, cracks appear in the water
Ah, suddenly
Oh, that's really...
Huh?
You laughed, right? You just laughed, right?
It's a joke
Ah!
It's not me
It's low, low, low
Yes, I did it, what should I do?
What should I do?
It's late, please go quickly.
The moon
Why are you here?
Ah, uh
From today, even the moon
It will help with the Gyesannyeon incident.
lump
The reason Dal is here
Is it related to your heart?
What is the heart
What kind of nonsense
ha
Neither am I?
Ha, who says what?
Well, in someone else’s inner situation
Stop paying attention
Is there news from the government?
Let me know, tsk.
The luggage owner's son
It feels alive.
The lie is
Just this once
I am a burnt person, after a fire in the year of Imjin.
An old man from Qingguk suddenly moved away.
I guessed it based on the circumstances.
The son of an old man from the Qing Dynasty
I think he's the son of Jimjo's owner.
That makes sense.
No, then right now.
Shouldn't I just bring it?
If you look at the letter
His whereabouts are unknown.
I think it will take some time to find it
If you're looking for that son
Make work easier
I think it can be solved
maybe
Sitting down before the national wedding
I might be able to break it down
Chi, to me
Even if my stomach sucks
I guess you don’t plan on having a national wedding.
Is Park Nain doing the national wedding?
huh?
Oh no, that
I, uh, I mean, I, uh
I don't plan on having a civil wedding.
You don't have a national wedding?
What does that mean?
No, that...
No, that's...
Well, no matter how much I think about it
- It doesn't seem to make sense...
- Brother
A
What is kimchi soup?
Are you saying that after eating it for the first time in a while?
That's it, I'm looking for the owner's son.
The son has conclusive evidence
This is possible only if you hold onto the upper left corner.
There's a month until the wedding.
Would you like to be in it?
Why rely on other people’s hopes?
Sprinkle ashes...
What does that mean?
Hiding your existence?
Brother
Did you know the language of the Qing Dynasty?
Hey, what...
Come and go a little...
The man who raised that beast was
where are you now
Some time after selling the baggage
A big fire broke out and the whole family was killed.
The luggage I had with me
I say my sin is burned away
Ugh...
Is this the owner's son?
That's...
Mr. Lee...
Doesn’t this need an explanation?
Let me explain
I can explain everything
ha
Hahaha
The man who betrayed me because of a woman
What kind of mouth can there be?
The moon is you!
Really because of Mr. Bean
Did you betray me?
Or any other circumstances...
Did you know?
To me
A long time ago, between the Grand Prince and Mr. Bean,
you knew
Whatever you say
At least make an excuse
I apologize.
As of today
Prince Jeun was involved in the Gyesannyeon incident.
Excluded
This Cheongguk boy
Take him away and investigate.
Why did Park Nine...
take that kid
yes
Wait a minute, let’s go together
Left injury
If you know the existence of the Cheongguk boy
will try to kill
Send it to Unjeong Palace
This is where I lived during the Saga period.
It would be worth hiding.
- degradation
- To Shinwon and Sedol
Record all the information the boy said
Bring it with you
And again...
Should I just cry? What else are you hiding?
I'm afraid you don't know that I'm upset?
I have no time to express my feelings
The luggage owner's son is in front of me.
Revenge is just around the corner
I can't believe I'm shaken by emotions like that.
It's not even possible
Pretending to be strong
Because I was hurt
The eyes and tip of the nose are bright red
So what?
What should I do if I’m upset?
Who wants me to do something?
What are you doing now...
um
It's times like this
I wanted someone to hug me
This is my body
I feel like that too now
You can lean on me
We share our bodies too
It's good to share hard work too.
If I hug you this hard
I feel like I'm falling apart
don't forget
between you and me
Even if you can't see it, there is a line
Hani
Don't cross the line
What if I pass it?
If it goes over, it's going to be a disaster, right?
you will regret it
There will be no turning back
Cheongguk boy
don't open your mouth
It's all in one piece
seems to be thinking
Boy, they say nothing is this easy.
no, so
Even though I'm accused of being a traitor
Have you been keeping your mouth shut?
아휴
아니, 뭐 한다고 이깟 건
이렇게 만드셔 가지고 이거
죽 쒀서 개도 못 줄 거
아니, 우희 아씨를 지키시든가
아싸리 좌상을 무너뜨려서
저하께 충성을 하시든가
원래 양측에
좋은 사람은 없는 겁니다
'좋은 사람'...
좋은 사람은 아니더라도
개새끼는 면해야지
당장 관복을 준비하게
예
what are you doing
I have to hide it
I have to hide it tightly
Why do I show my regrets
Let’s send Dal out.
just talk
It is said that the seated figure still has a sense of belonging.
There is a basis
Yeah? What is it?
Have you found out where Jimjo is?
Oh my
I was so smart
The moon is more crazy about you
Okay, tell me.
What is the basis for that?
The boy from the Qing Dynasty thinks he was deceived by me.
I won't open my mouth easily
Even if I open my mouth
I can't guarantee it's true
In this book
What the boy said about Jimjo
I have all the information
before that
Please make a promise
Even if the statue collapses
Please save Woohee
That...
leave this behind
After thinking, I will give you a message.
You have to make a promise to give it to me.
Me and I who have already lost someone dear to us
Among you who want to protect
Who is more desperate?
after reflection
I will give you an answer about Mr. Bean.
So leave this book
Just go back now
Hey, Grand Prince Nari
Why did you write that book?
uh? I'm going to betray you anyway
What did you use it for?
I just kinda
I wanted to postpone it
If you break down the statue
Woohee becomes a slave
If you leave the seat as is
My brother is in danger.
ha
Because I don't know what to do
Then you should have caught one of the two.
I beg you that I did something wrong
I can't do things like revenge
Things like books
I should have burned it down or something.
What is this?
If you pray
I betrayed my brother
They said it would disappear?
Those who burned books
The horrible things I said to Woohee
Would you like to pick it up?
I am always a coward
A cowardly man has no choice
Hmm, this is truly cowardly.
All this risk
Even though I know it’s because of me
It's like you're hurting me
Is cowardice a strength?
Ha, what is this?
Are you becoming more and more cruel?
Wow
It's tiny, it's tiny, tsk
This is done with sincerity
Is it right to see it?
I can't write something like this with a heart that will betray me
amman
Uh huh, hmm
- line
- Huh? Yeah
Ayu, ayu, ayu, ii
I understand, I understand, ing
Uh, now, now, now, now, now, good, ing?
I made a line, okay?
Don't cross the line
Tsk, tsk
Hmm
no, what
Did you get any new information?
um
After harvesting Jimdog,
Toxicity disappears within three days
The left statue had Joseon as a gift.
I would have abandoned that burden
It's not a strain
I'm sure I'm still worried
will have
Jeonyu
Because of the co-sleeping incident
When I almost became a government official
Your Majesty told me
Is that what you said?
Don't confront the left person
The Gyesannyeon incident
It's not over yet
If you think about it carefully, it
Doesn't that mean Jimjo is alive?
Hmm, maybe
Now the purpose is clear
find jimjo
uncovering its owner
Then what?
The Gyesanyeon incident was caused by Jim Dog.
Prove that it was poisoning
Jimjo's owner
The real culprit of the Gyesanyeon incident
I have to reveal that he is a traitor.
No matter how bad it is
You won't be able to escape the crime of treason.
No, then
Evidence gathered so far
Autopsy report on Gyesannyeon’s body
What, hey
I have all these documents.
Now all I have to do is grab my luggage.
Hmm, I need more proof.
Living in a private estate
Jimjo must be captured alive.
Oh, then the private land of Mr.
I guess I can search.
I thought you wouldn't come, brother.
Long time no see, Captain Left.
Can you treat me comfortably like before?
Isn't there any?
Now I
My old brother
I can't see you anymore
I lost my beloved younger brother.
The reason you came to see me today
What is it?
bakgadali
He used to be a backpack seller in Boryeong.
It's a child
my wife's niece
How do you know?
It's strange
If you are the old man's niece
It must be a happy meal
As a backpacker and a naegwan
Now I am a court lady
The court lady of Donggungjeon.
In times like these
Something scarier than your mouth
Would you be in nothingness?
I lost my parents and my livelihood is at a loss.
I heard that they do this and that.
I don't think they're that close.
It was like that
Maybe the captain
I don't know if you know, but
The moon is that child
I found my girlfriend
So
I also treat that child like my wife.
I will protect you with my life.
I made a promise
Fearless and fierce
I thought it was a child
There was a part of me that believed
I
If you touch that child
Me too
I don't think I'll stay still
Somehow
My brother asked me to
I said you responded very easily.
To warn you today
You came out, right?
If you do
I've finished what I had to say
I'll just go back now
Look, Hancheol.
Are you satisfied now?
I'm satisfied now
stop here
If you go further
No matter how deep revenge is, it is meaningless.
What kind of revenge
Will there be satisfaction?
Oh, what is it?
Well, I'm not saying I'm taking sides.
Chi
You're no longer on my side
No, well, to be honest,
Without even guaranteeing Mr. Bean’s safety.
Well, that's just the information
Skipping eating too
It's a kind of backstabbing.
I haven't dared to risk anything until now.
Will people of conscience hold me back?
I don't care if you're cowardly
I don't care if it's rude
What if I'm a coward, huh?
Ah, kinda
Well, what if it's lethal?
ha
The bad guys
Do bad things like eat a meal
Just like pooping in the sky
It only brings hardships
Don't you become mean to people and hate them?
Isn't it shrinking?
It's okay for you
Even if I become cowardly, even if I become cruel
Please shrink down for a moment.
All the award winners
Even if I throw stones at you
Getting stoned now
To Genie
And so ruthlessly
It breaks people's hearts
Huh? No, what, what?
line
Chi, ayu, yeah, yeah, what, really
Oh, why? very just
They tell me to go outside
Why, ing? Chi
Go away
as far as possible
Mandeok, let’s eat some food.
Oh my, oh my
Wow, so cute
Wow, the dog's arms are the upper arms.
The people are not even allowed to watch
Eat all the meat, okay?
What are you doing in the country?
There must be a lot of complaints?
no
I do it because I'm jealous, because I'm jealous
Who gives in this wide palace
I'm just eating and eating.
More than most people
Aren’t you a good seller? Hmm
Oh no
Me too
If you bring me a meal...
Let’s sell the dog?
you are telling me now
Did you say ‘let’s sell the dog’?
no
Don't say it to me, it's Jimjo, Jimjo.
I heard that Jwasang raised it?
No, that kind of guy
I just released it somewhere
I won't raise it
That trapped guy
How can I eat rice?
This is what I'm trying to say now
Well, who will get it?
Asking the obvious, tsk
luggage manager
Ingredients from the top of Cheonghye
It's a precious health ingredient.
I'll keep it separate
Ah, low
Please find this shabby place
A great light is coming
Things like poisonous insects
Where do you get it?
Ordinary people can't catch it.
Landmen and magazines
Landlords in the city
I have to meet you first.
Oh, go ahead and go
What should I ask?
Are you asking me if I want to feed my luggage?
Let me ask you if you know Chorang Tal?
If you do
What should I do?
Hey, Ji again
Ah!
Swallow, an astounded grounder
Did you catch one?
Uh, yeah, yeah
Oh, but how do you know me...
You look familiar
The other day at the doctor's office
Haven't you seen it?
He said he recognized Jim Dog.
Oh my goodness
Where can you find such poison, yes?
Oh, well, I don't know if it's Jim Dog...
Ah, yes, a clinic famous for acupuncture.
Now I remember, um
Hang Ah
I heard that Hang Ah saved it.
What if I remember now?
So, yeah
Not me, but you
I feel like I just remembered
Ah, I just remembered
But the landman
Aren’t you here to see it?
Ah, the original lawmakers and land workers
They are very friendly.
Now, this is
No, this is
It will be a great help
helpful information
I hope you get it
What?
Not a jar
Let's go
Why?
Ah, I hate it
We are the landmen
If you meet and go around
It will soon reach your left ear.
And relatively less surveillance.
you are the best
Well, let's go together, okay?
Do you know?
- Brother, do you know?
- Moller
Oh, I don't know, I don't know
Oh, we don't know
Again?
ha
Go, go
Hey, do you know what this is?
It doesn't seem to be the case this time either...
Well, look closely.
More details, huh?
Now, don't you see?
I don’t know, I really don’t know.
Okay, go
Fly away
I don't know anyone anyway
Go away, go!
just one more time
give me a chance
Ah
I found it in Bak Ga Dal's place.
I think it could be seen as a love letter
Yeonseogun to Jeundaegun
There is no mention of Prince Jeun.
Blood can't fool you
You and your girlfriend
A court lady in love
I will do it
I will do anything
Please save Migeum.
This time for sure
I will give you fertility medication.
Get rid of it
There's something to check
They tell me to just give her fertility medication.
Didn't you?
I felt weak thinking about the past for a while
If you get caught up in the past
There's no way to move forward
That face that looks so much like an abandoned bin
It's annoying
How can two families
It's a line portrait at one o'clock in one day
Oh, I can't even speak
How can an old mother live alone?
That's right
Bongchim
Because it doesn't seem to react
I don't think it's poison
How come it's not poison?
Two families dying at the same time?
If it dies from poisoning
The body swells or rots black...
No reaction to silver
The body does not rot to black
It's Jimdog
In this case, the investigation
No signs of external intrusion
No poison was found
Shouldn’t it be viewed as a question word?
‘Suspicious death’
I have to fill out an autopsy report.
- Move the body to Pocheong.
- Damn it
yes
Excuse me
lump
Have you ever seen interest?
eww...
Ugh...
I'm not here to harm you.
I'm here to help you
Uh, uh...
interest
You killed your family, right?
I too am looking for interest
The boss
They killed my family too
So can you tell me?
Everything I know about interest
So I can get revenge by taking interest
So that I can avenge you
Ah, uh, mmmm...
ah
Ugh, ah, ah!
Argh!
This fragrance
Is it interest?
Uh, what?
Um, Your Highness is looking for you?
I can't avoid it today
Oh my, the desk is so useless, the desk is
What?
yes?
Oh, it's nothing
But why did you call me?
Bakga Dal-i to the royal palace
Even though I was kidnapped
Still haven't realized anything?
Yes, yes?
Lead, kidnapping...?
The child is ready to die
He said he refused fertility medication and fought.
Isn’t the crown prince ashamed?
one here
It looks like it has some kind of drug on it.
No...
If you do it then...
Oh, no way
Didn't you know?
yes
I didn't know
I am
I didn't know anything
Please give a donation.
That's it
The karma of this life
It seems like a lot
If it's not a gift, it's a wedding...
What are you talking about?
Huh?
Ah, why are you here?
- You damn bitch.
- Ah!
Why are you here?
Uhm, stay still, ying
What is this...
Why is this falling?
Bow your head
That's a bit sloppy
Go talk to where you're stuck
There are only three people running away here.
- Yeah, uh, definitely.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, wait a minute.
Where are you taking me?
Why suddenly...
Honey, you're not hurt, right?
Where does it hurt?
Ah, the body.
He's fine, but...
Give it back, ying
Or maybe you met someone
So what did you remember?
You didn't do it, right?
Let's meet
I met you everywhere
Well, I don't remember anything in particular.
Yo
That's it then
Tie it up
- Ying
- Tied up? What are you tying?
What, why, why are you tying me up?
What is this, what is this? This...
Can't you solve this right now?
I heard you have to go into the palace!
Yiing
You go to the Qingguk, not the palace.
Cheongguk, Cheongguk.
Well, what nonsense is that...
When you say something nice
Can't you solve this?
Does the moon want to take a nap?
How can you sleep in this situation?
How much of this should I feed?
- Um...
- If you feed them all of this,
- Oh, I...
- Does it work?
It shouldn't work
Song Jang can't get on the ship.
- Ah
- Yes
Cow, cow, cow, invoice?
Cow, cow, song...
Please put a flue in the palace, in the palace.
Please call the Crown Prince!
How does the moon know how old you are?
Could it be that you met the Crown Prince?
Yeah, no
yes
The Crown Prince is my successor.
There is no need to run away to the Qing Dynasty.
What is this...
Uh, when did it disappear?
what?
Baby, don't touch
I didn't touch it
True
- Huh?
- Ugh
Ah, who is this?
Oh, how much I missed you
Ah, the Crown Prince
Wow
Ah, what are you doing?
Ah, inna, inna, huh?
It's me, Tusk, your father's daughter, the moon
Huh?
No, not the moon
How can she not even be a daughter...
- Son Indie
- Uh
How did this happen...
You!
No...
you
Ah, so
The moon covered the scars on your wrists
The Crown Prince caught him.
The light flashed and I fell into the water.
Your body changed?
What kind of birth story is this?
why? You came out with a lot of eggs, right?
Hey, hey, hey
Why doesn't the dragon fly?
Wings in the armpits
I don’t know why it’s not sprouting, huh?
Wow
Is that my daughter's triple bottom?
No
The way you speak can change as much as you like.
What kind of plague are you carrying?
huh?
Write it, Bonnie.
This soft, sparkling eye glow
My daughter’s eyes are pretty, huh?
- Wow, you're crazy.
- Huh? why?
Crown Prince, please kill me.
I'm sorry, my dear.
It's a mark where Hongyeon was sealed.
Hongyeon was forced to quit
If I meet my partner again and feel shaken up
I can't help it then
Sonega
committed disloyalty
Oh no
Everyone go out
Come with me for a moment
Talk about it
Hmm
Okay, close it.
- Ah, no.
- Child, low
Oh no
We, we, we...
Ah, that, that, this, this way...
degradation
Now tell me
The moon is on my wrist scar
There is something, right?
a long time ago
The moon once fell into the water
Then suddenly on my wrist
I got a red scar.
And then I lose my memory
It was a car that I found strange.
'water'
There's definitely something in the water.
What else can I do?
Was there anything more strange?
Tell me everything you know
I hope the moon comes back to you too
Aren't you hoping for it?
What I know is
That's it.
That, our tusks, my uncle
Even if I ran away
Those are definitely bad people
No.
Why do you say that?
Falling in love is not a sin
That...
It's cheap, even though it has a bitter sound to it.
What kind of heart is
It can be a sin
Ah, it's a sin, but
Ji-ga saved my life and, ah,
What has changed so much in my body?
I don't think it's a normal relationship.
Well, just looking at it, huh?
Will I hurt your family?
Are you worried?
No, I can't move
Please imprison me in Unjeong Palace.
confinement
I'm protecting it.
Left injury
I know about Park Gaekju.
Maybe they'll take your family hostage
I thought you might scare me
Boy, I didn't even know I was losing
Wow, I was scared for no reason.
Ah, why are you always so sick?
Landworkers and their families
died of poison
How cruel
How should the rest live?
It's because of me
Even if I hadn't been wandering around
They were people who couldn't die.
Why is that because of the drop?
Is there someone else who killed it?
I hate myself for always missing out.
Even those who need to be protected
I am no one else
You couldn't protect it.
You protected it.
I was taken away by the manufacturing merchant.
I almost took fertility pills
You protected me.
I could have been dragged to death.
Fight until the end
You protected it.
how did you know that
I didn't want you to know
I heard everything from the Great Queen Mother.
no
Just drink the infertility medicine.
Why are we fighting, why are we fighting?
Then when something big happens,
How should I live?
Chi
What is that, like crystal?
If you drink that, your dreams will become
Put on flower shoes and settle down, your real family
What's going to happen with all that?
At best
Did you fight because of those words?
How can that be all?
It's your dream
Why on earth is that like that?
Just for the rest of my life
My hair is white, my memories are black
I told you to live like a winter night like that.
Why is it raining flowers like this?
Why did you let me down the flower road?
You keep saying that to me
You keep saying that...
My memory keeps getting weaker.
I chewed it thoroughly and ate it.
I keep feeling sad and unfair
So I want to be comforted
And I wish it were that bad
ridiculous
You start looking forward to it.
What expectations?
Hey, do you like it?
degradation
I'm sorry, but I'm sorry.
I will follow you
Uh...
no
No, for what crime?
Are you saying you're going to arrest me?
Regardless of the crime
How dare you in front of the Crown Prince?
Are you going to arrest the palace staff of Donggungjeon?
Are you telling me to humiliate Utjeon now?
How dare a small person
Would you commit such disloyalty?
Soin, I'm just following the orders.
What do you mean by ‘Eomyeong’?
Prince Jeun and Donggung Nain
Have you committed adultery?
In that Nine place
A gift has been received
What kind of testimony is this?
Is it important?
What's important is
It's not about what kind of testimony it is.
How should we punish those two?
I've already decided to do that.
My beliefs are just
charge and degradation
I just wish you goodbye
Ha, it's fornication.
What kind of nonsense is this?
Is this a frame-up?
At Prince Jeun’s private residence before entering the palace.
You stayed, right?
Also recently
At Jeundaegun’s private residence
Going into the late hours of the night
There is someone who saw it
That was an errand for the Crown Prince...
Yes you bitch!
How dare you
Are you talking about the crown prince and his descendants?
If you do this too
Written by the Crown Prince
Would you call it a seochal?
I recognize you.
This is a love letter you wrote to Prince Jeun.
‘Jeundaegun’...
Are you kidding me?
Where do you see this?
Is this a love letter sent to Prince Jeun?
This is now
Do you think I'm the only one who messes with this?
don't worry
Prince Jeundae is probably in the middle of the country right now.
I'm so happy
Chief Left Officer
Do you like me?
Why are you so obsessed with me?
That's right
My eyes keep going to the Prince.
ha
Why do you have so much power?
Are people becoming obvious?
To my mom too
To me too
Chi
no
I have to do my best to insist
What kind of love letter is this?
What?
Moreover, the opponent is Prince Jeun?
Wow, what nonsense is this?
If you look at that letter
Prince Jeun and Bak Ga Dal-i
There is a phrase that calls itself
Ha, what, what, what, huh? What
'The night is black and the moon is bright'
‘Why does it look like it’s full of clouds?
'Is my mind blurry?'
What is this one line?
It's a cure for constipation?
Chi, if you shake it off and no dust comes out,
Well, let’s make some fluff
I'll take a look at it. Is this a sign like that?
A report came in
In Bakga Dal’s place
A love letter was found
This is the work of court ladies.
Dealing with it according to the rules of the court ladies
I think it's right
Okay, I'll leave this book behind.
Haona
Why?
I'm afraid they'll steal my letter
Are you worried?
That letter
I'll tell you that Ji wrote it.
Anyway, poor handwriting
If you say you wrote that letter
At the Great King's Battle, they used that as an excuse.
He will take you into his concubine.
If you refuse
Asked about the crime of rejecting the crown prince's favor
I will behead you.
You must be scared
No, just a piece of paper.
Even beheading
A palace is that kind of place.
A piece of paper can mean the difference between life and death
a heartless place
Hani
do nothing
Me or Jeundaegun
There will be no need to admit it
They say it's neither of them
They say it won't end
What are you guys going to do?
Oh no
From kidnapping to infertility pills
Did you mean to be Meg?
Will you leave me alone?
I, uh, I have to do something...
In an unwanted marriage
If you take a concubine you don't like,
my heart
If you do that, I'll just leave.
please make a pact with me
You are
You can't protect the moon.
So, when my body comes back, without hesitation
Without any regrets
please send me moon
my heart
I shouldn't let you sit down
I have to hide it tightly
no hair visible
So that not even a shadow can be seen
Like this
I guess my body has changed
Let me get hurt instead of you
Having experienced all this humiliation myself,
Out of guilt for poverty
Don't go away
Poor mom, remind me of your guilt
Body changed manger?
All three awards are centered around you.
I know you're spinning around
In my life, I’m the main character
Num's life
In my love story
Don't use it as a prop.
Suddenly what...
To protect land prices from falling
The reason for coming forward
Protecting myself
They say it’s to protect yourself.
I didn't know how to take care of myself if I lost
I didn't know how to take care of others.
Mix it up
It's a punishment from heaven
Do you understand?
- Sedol
- Yes?
I wrote it to the poor
Something like a diary or love letter
Do you know where it is?
Ah, ah, if that's the case
It'll be over here.
- uh?
- This way
Ah, it's dark under the lamp
Is this a safe or something?
Why are you asking me that?
You put it in
um
Phew
Huh? What is this?
That...
Huh?
No...
Isn't it mine now?
So I will do whatever I want.
No, why is this here...
You picked it up and brought it to me.
Why are you asking me that again?
here
This is the diary I wrote to my poor mother.
But this suddenly
Why are you looking for it?
The love letter that says the moon is a blessing for evil spirits
i wrote
Why are you so surprised?
Not the moon
I must have written it to the poor.
If I show you this
Dal-i’s false accusation
you can peel it off
If you reveal that it is a love letter written by you,
Will the Great King go over?
somehow weave it together
I think he's going to kill his concubine right away.
First, we need to put out the urgent fire.
Sleepless all the time
It's not comfortable
I thought it was a bedding
I guess it's the heart
The night is black and the moon is bright
Why does my heart feel like it’s filled with clouds?
Is it blurry?
I am not me
Are you not you too?
In the lost place
I lie down with my feet stretched out with only a blunt longing
I wonder if I can find what I lost
Should I go back to my place?
Then and only then
Is there peace?
Maybe this heart
Not a poor mom
Maybe it's me
What's going on?
In Bakga Dal’s place
Exchanged with Prince Jeun
I heard that Yeonseo is coming out.
I'm telling you to do this and risk that child's life
Do you know that you saved my life?
How dare this person
The sin of humiliation and betrayal
I will ask firmly
I wrote that book
Now the crown prince is telling the child
Did you say you wrote a love letter?
Oh, yes?
Yeon, not Yeonseo
It was just poetry
The crown prince has that child in his heart.
Even though I wrote poetry to woo you
Did that child reject Seung-eun?
The crown prince's victory
Ask for the sin of refusing
I will behead you.
You must be scared
Say it, Crown Prince!
The moon has never refused
If you do this, the moon will beat that child.
Are you going to take me into your concubine?
yes
To the moon
I will take you into my harem.
Lady Yoon!
Yes mama
Let’s go right now
Release it quickly
I will make you a concubine.
That's...
Guseokgung to Bakga Dal-i
He was sentenced to fetal punishment.
Fetal type?
Right now!
Ugh
Ah...
Dear Crown Prince!
deterioration, degradation
degradation
come to your senses
body
My body is back
yes
You're back
I'm back
Put it on
Please kill me
Are you coming?
I'll kill you all
From now on, I
It's your shield
You hide behind me
To the crown prince
don't give your heart
You have to steal to be loved and survive
Cesar
Are you saying kill me?
Under Inwangsan Mountain
I have a drinking degree.
What should I do with my weak heart?
Have you created a weakness again?
- It's mom!
- Sweet
You are like this
Running like a moon
I have no choice but to chase my Prince Jeun far away.
This bonsai
Cutting it well is a virtue.
Don't go astray
Don't get twisted
I have to cut my flesh and conform
You can survive
My father always said
It blooms at the highest point in Joseon.
live as a flower
I came to bow down
Like my father said
I will live like a flower
Please save Prince Jeun.